Diane Di Prima Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Correspondence, undated, 1967-1990
  - Subseries A: Incoming, undated, 1967-1990
    - Katz, Vincent, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 196)
    - Keller, Lynn, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 197)
    - Keller, Vickie, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 198)
    - Kelly, Robert, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 199)
    - Kimmelman, Burt, 1986 (Box 6:, Folder 200)
    - Kincaid, Dianna, 1986-1987 (Box 6:, Folder 201)
    - King, Martha, [1990?] (Box 6:, Folder 202)
    - Kirschenbaum, Blossom, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 203)
    - Knight, Arthur and Kit, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 204)
    - Knoll, Zig, 1981 (Box 6:, Folder 205)
    - Kocik, Robert, undated (Box 6:, Folder 206)
    - Kolokithas, Dawn, undated (Box 6:, Folder 207)
    - Kowit, Steve, 1987-1988 (Box 6:, Folder 208)
    - Krohn, Vicki, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 209)
    - Lasher, Diane, 1983 (Box 6:, Folder 210)
    - Lebel, Jean-Jacques, 1976 (Box 6:, Folder 211)
    - LeCuyer, James, undated, 1990 (Box 6:, Folder 212)
    - Lester, Rusty, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 213)
    - Levi-Strauss, David, undated, 1986-1986 (Box 6:, Folder 214)
    - Levitt, Peter, undated (Box 6:, Folder 215)
    - Lifshin, Lyn, undated, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 216)
    - Lorde, Audre, 1986 (Box 6:, Folder 217)
    - Lowenstein, Michael, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 218)
    - Luiz, Charlene, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 219)
    - Lynch, Michael, 1987 (Box 6:, Folder 220)
    - Magnuson, Sally, 1989 (Box 6:, Folder 221)
    - Mahoney, Dennis, 1988 (Box 6:, Folder 222)
    - Malone, Marvin, undated (Box 6:, Folder 223)
    - Marley, Elsa, 1983-1990 (Box 6:, Folder 224)
    - Marlowe, Alan, 1968-1989 (Box 7:, Folder 225)
    - Masullo, Robert, 1987 (Box 7:, Folder 226)
    - Matson, Clive, 1984 (Box 7:, Folder 227)
    - Mayo, Michael, 1984 (Box 7:, Folder 228)
    - McGilvery, Larry, 1971 (Box 7:, Folder 229)
    - McLean, Adam, Hermetic Journal, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 230)
    - McNaughton, Duncan, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 231)
    - McNaughton, John, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 232)
    - McWilliams, Christine, 1987 (Box 7:, Folder 233)
    - Meador, Betty, undated, 1983, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 234)
    - Meecham, James/Caprice, 1987, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 235)
    - Meehan, Maude, 1988-1989 (Box 7:, Folder 236)
    - Meiskey, Elinor, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 237)
    - Metzger, Deena, undated, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 238)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review, 1989-1990 (Box 7:, Folder 239)
    - Mines, Stephanie, 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 240)
    - Molloy, Alice, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 241)
    - Moyer, Elizabeth, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 242)
    - Mueller, Jack/National Poetry Week, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 243)
    - Murdock, Maureen, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 244)
    - Murgia, Sulvy, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 245)
    - Murphy, Stanley, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 246)
    - Musser, James/Skyline Books, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 247)
    - Myman, Barbara, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 248)
    - National Poetry Association, Inc., 1986-1990 (Box 7:, Folder 249)
    - National Poetry Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 7:, Folder 250)
    - National Poetry Musem, 1987 (Box 7:, Folder 251)
    - New Directions, 1985 (Box 7:, Folder 252)
    - New York Quarterly, 1987 (Box 7:, Folder 253)
    - Newgarden, Albert, 1988 (Box 7:, Folder 254)
    - Nintzel, Hans, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 255)
    - No More Censorship Defense Fund, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 256)
    - North Atlantic Books/“Io”, undated, 1976-1980 (Box 7:, Folder 257)
    - Notus, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 258)
    - Oakley, Carolyn, 1990 (Box 7:, Folder 259)
    - Oldenburg, Patty, undated (Box 7:, Folder 260)
    - Olympia Press/Maurice Girodias, 1969-1972 (Box 7:, Folder 261)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1967, 1985 (Box 7:, Folder 262)
    - Orenstein, Gloria, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 263)
    - Ostriker, Alicia, 1986 (Box 7:, Folder 264)
    - Pacifica Radio/Jennifer Stone, 1989 (Box 7:, Folder 265)
    - Paley, Grace, 1986 (Box 8:, Folder 266)
    - Palmer, Michael, 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 267)
    - Paragon house, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 268)
    - Parker, Alice, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 269)
    - Parker, Frankie Edith Kerouac, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 270)
    - Parrish, Larayne, undated (Box 8:, Folder 271)
    - Patchen, Miriam, 1978 (Box 8:, Folder 272)
    - Patler, Louis, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 273)
    - Peace Press, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 274)
    - Pelosi, Nancy, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 275)
    - Perkins, William/ Howl, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 276)
    - Perrizo, James E., 1986-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 277)
    - Piercy, Marge, 1985-1987 (Box 8:, Folder 278)
    - Pine, Evelyn, undated (Box 8:, Folder 279)
    - Plamondon, Kevin, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 280)
    - Poetry Center, 1986-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 281)
    - Poetry New York, undated (Box 8:, Folder 282)
    - Poetry Project/Gary Lenhart, et. al., 1985-1988 (Box 8:, Folder 283)
    - Poets & Writers, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 284)
    - Pollack, Rachel, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 285)
    - Pomada, Elizabeth, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 286)
    - Ponce, Charles, 1977-1979 (Box 8:, Folder 287)
    - Postman, Bruce, undated, 1983 (Box 8:, Folder 288)
    - Powell, Sheppard, undated, ca. 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 289)
    - Pratt, Norwood, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 290)
    - Prossnall, Bob, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 291)
    - Prism International/Mary Cameron, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 292)
    - Project Outward Bound, 1984 (Box 8:, Folder 293)
    - Raffetto, Sara, 1989-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 294)
    - Rand, Yvonne, undated (Box 8:, Folder 295)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 296)
    - Rawles, Richard, 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 297)
    - Rhodes, Kimberly S., 1986 (Box 8:, Folder 298)
    - Rhone, Christine, 1982-1987 (Box 8:, Folder 299)
    - Roark, Randy, 1984-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 300)
    - Robertson, David, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 301)
    - Roche, Jud, 1988-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 302)
    - Rodin, Renee, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 303)
    - Romano, Rose/La Bella Figura, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 304)
    - Roskos, David, [1988] (Box 8:, Folder 305)
    - Rosset, Barney/Blue Moon Books, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 306)
    - Roth, Martha, undated (Box 8:, Folder 307)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, undated, 1984 (Box 8:, Folder 308)
    - Russo, Richard, 1986 (Box 8:, Folder 309)
    - Ryulin, Janet, 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 310)
    - Sacramento Poetry Center, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 311)
    - St. Lawrence University, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 312)
    - St. Mane, Diana, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 313)
    - San Francisco School of Art, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 314)
    - Sawyer, Paul, 1988-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 315)
    - Sbroca, Josephina, 1990 (Box 8:, Folder 316)
    - Schmitz, Dennis, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 317)
    - Schneider, David, undated (Box 8:, Folder 318)
    - Schumacher, Michael, 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 319)
    - Scott, Andrew Murray, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 320)
    - Sebasco, Raul Santiago, 1983 (Box 8:, Folder 321)
    - Setterfield, Velda, undated (Box 8:, Folder 322)
    - Shapiro, Howard, 1984 (Box 8:, Folder 323)
    - Short, David, 1989 (Box 8:, Folder 324)
    - Shurin, Aaron, 1988 (Box 8:, Folder 325)
    - Silberg, richard, undated (Box 8:, Folder 326)
    - Silliman, Ron, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 327)
    - Simon Fraser University Library, 1986 (Box 8:, Folder 328)
    - Simon-Ross, Celia, 1985 (Box 8:, Folder 329)
    - Small Press Distribution, 1989-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 330)
    - Smith, Sterret, 1982 (Box 8:, Folder 331)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1987 (Box 8:, Folder 332)
    - Sobelman, Annah, 1988-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 333)
    - Society of the Muse of the Southwest, 1985-1989 (Box 8:, Folder 334)
    - Solomon, Carl, 1989-1990 (Box 8:, Folder 335)
    - Solomon, Norman, undated, 1988 (Box 9:, Folder 336)
    - Speck, Rick, 1986 (Box 9:, Folder 337)
    - Spur of the Moment, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 338)
    - Stanley, George, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 339)
    - Stark-Smith, Nancy, 1988-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 340)
    - Stearns, Ethie, undated (Box 9:, Folder 341)
    - Stewart, Dodie, 1988, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 342)
    - Straits, 1982 (Box 9:, Folder 343)
    - Strohm, Colleen, undated, 1987 (Box 9:, Folder 344)
    - Sudden Jungle Press, 1985 (Box 9:, Folder 345)
    - Sumrall, Amber Coverdale, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 346)
    - Sussex, Alan, 1986 (Box 9:, Folder 347)
    - Sutherland, Joan, undated, 1986 (Box 9:, Folder 348)
    - Sweeney, Kathleen/Snake Power, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 349)
    - Swendiman, Steve, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 350)
    - Sykes, Michael, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 351)
    - Symington, Julie, undated, 1987 (Box 9:, Folder 352)
    - Tart, Indrek, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 353)
    - Thompson, Scott, undated (Box 9:, Folder 354)
    - Torrey, E. Fuller, 1982 (Box 9:, Folder 355)
    - Turtle Island Press, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 356)
    - University of California at Berkeley, 1988 (Box 9:, Folder 357)
    - University of California at Berkeley/Art Museum, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 358)
    - Van Hallie, Jean-Claude, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 359)
    - Van Ham, Lane, undated (Box 9:, Folder 360)
    - Van Ornum, William E., 1983-1984 (Box 9:, Folder 361)
    - Waldman, Anne L., 1987-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 362)
    - Waldman, John, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 363)
    - Walter, Zoe, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 364)
    - Wedge, George, 1987 (Box 9:, Folder 365)
    - Weed, Susan, undated (Box 9:, Folder 366)
    - Weigle, Marta, 1982 (Box 9:, Folder 367)
    - Wilentz, Ted, 1987 (Box 9:, Folder 368)
    - Willis, Liz, 1988 (Box 9:, Folder 369)
    - Willner, Phyllis, 1981 (Box 9:, Folder 370)
    - Wilson, Bob, 1978-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 371)
    - Wilson, Peter, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 372)
    - Wilson, Shari-D., 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 373)
    - Wingbow Press, 1979-1989 (Box 9:, Folder 374)
    - Winson, Robert, 1989 (Box 9:, Folder 375)
    - Woodard, Dennis, undated, 1986 (Box 9:, Folder 376)
    - Wright, Margaret, 1990 (Box 9:, Folder 377)
    - Writers and Books, 1986 (Box 9:, Folder 378)
  - Subseries B: Outgoing, undated, 1976-1990
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 9:, Folder 379)
    - Wilson, Robert, 1976 (Box 9:, Folder 380)
    - Upton,?, ca. 1978-1984 (Box 9:, Folder 381)
    - 1985 January - 1986 December (Box 9:, Folder 382)
    - 1987 January - October (Box 9:, Folder 383)
    - 1987 November - 1988 April (Box 10:, Folder 384)
    - 1988 May - October (Box 10:, Folder 385)
    - 1988 October - November (Box 10:, Folder 386)
    - 1988 December - 1989 February (Box 10:, Folder 387)
    - 1989 March (Box 10:, Folder 388)
    - 1989 April (Box 10:, Folder 389)
    - 1989 May (Box 10:, Folder 390)
    - 1989 June - July (Box 10:, Folder 391)
    - 1989 August (Box 10:, Folder 392)
    - 1989 September (Box 10:, Folder 393)
    - 1989 October (Box 11:, Folder 394)
    - 1989 November (Box 11:, Folder 395)
    - 1989 December (Box 11:, Folder 396)
    - Marlowe, Alan, undated, 1985-1989 (Box 11:, Folder 397)
    - 1990 (Box 11:, Folder 398)
  - Subseries C: Other Correspondence, undated, 1985-1990
    - Marlowe, Alan, 1989 (Box 11:, Folder 399)
    - Morales, Karla (for Di Prima), undated, 1983-1990 (Box 11:, Folder 400)
    - Third Party, undated (Box 11:, Folder 401)
- Series IV: Photographs and Audio Materials, undated
  - Materials separated from correspondence, undated (Box 11:, Folder 403)
- Series V: Ephemera, undated, ca. 1980-1990
  - Flyers, pamphlets, brochures, etc. (Box 12:, Folder 404-407)